Explore banks and the product.
Which one is faster?
Reduce.
Let's try.
Why?
You can see it clearly even if you just open it.
I have already opened it.
Don't tease me.
Nice.
Dark to light of the night.
It looks like a movie.
Nice.
Are these values pre-populated?
Did you just put them in?
They are already there.
This is how it is.
If I open this page, I can directly click on it.
Perfect.
Is this the product name?
It is the name of the team.
Nice.
This is how it is.
Do you know how to do this?
There are two buttons.
Public and private.
What is this?
You have given an all button,
a public button and a private button.
Instead,
Public and private.
Both are ticked by default.
All is not a separate filter.
Both of these filters are chosen by default.
What is the difference?
Why do we need a button?
This is Apple's button.
I feel the same when I press and hold one button.
I have seen this.
I have seen this on Amazon.
I have seen this everywhere.
But this button...
I am a little confused. What is this button?
All the checkboxes.
Yes.
It is very easy.
Instead, public and private.
Both are selected by default.
All.
All is not a separate selection.
And the weight is also the same.
Floating is fixed.
Floating is selected by default.
Why do we need a separate button?
And the same here.
Then,
it becomes uniform.
This block.
So,
these filters
make a little gap.
And this gap
makes you feel
that this is the heading
of your section.
And this is the subheading of this section.
And it works.
It works.
These gaps actually work.
But there are no such checkboxes.
There are many even widgets.
Does this happen when you open it?
It happens when you click from your mobile.
From the desktop.
What is the matter?
What are the concessions?
First name on the property
means index 2 is the first.
Means,
there can be multiple names on the property.
She has to be one of them.
One of them.
Nice, bro.
Is this blue?
No back.
Where is the back?
This is mobile.
She has to be an individual.
You shouldn't take this to someone else.
Write in the concessions
that this is not the case.
You can get 0.05
to 0.3
or 0.2
means you can give them the entire range
of total discounts.
And some concessions
can even stack up.
Like woman and greenhouse.
But each of
these options also need
to have their own eye
information. Because
why take it to someone else?
Because I need to know
what insurance concessions are.
And you don't even need to write
Not even here.
The public has it.
Usually
the public application process
is a little difficult.
It is difficult.
Complete service
end-to-end service is
not good. But
the rate is 0.5.
Private
service is not that good.
But the rates are not as good as public.
Processing fee is also not that good.
Tell me
what should I select?
And you keep both of them selected by default.
Same here. You tell me
the trade-offs here only.
Why I should select each of them?
For floating and fixed.
What is an order of
an order of facility?
There is a normal loan
which is linked
to your savings account.
If you have
taken a loan of 20 lakhs
in the savings bank
and you have kept 5 lakhs
in your savings account,
you need interest of 15 lakhs.
And you can take out 5 lakhs
or you can keep it.
But
it gives you liberty
to keep your extra money
and take less interest.
But you have to pay more
than 0.25 interest.
Those who have a lot of cash
and want to keep the money,
they can keep it there.
I don't have any other option.
Nice, nice, nice.
You should explain it like this.
We should learn this.
It is very important.